Contact

txsrn@icloud.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sarahmckelvey-130228113 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Patient Safety Hospitals

Certifications
TNCC Instructor
Registered Nurse

Sarah McKelvey

Corporate Health Nurse at JPMorgan Chase & Co. Montgomery, Texas

Summary

Experienced Emergency Room Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Emergency Medicine, Certified Emergency Nurse (CEN), Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Emergency Nursing Pediatric Course (ENPC), Trauma Nursing Core Curriculum (TNCC) certification and Instructor, Patient Safety, Nursing, and Critical Care Nursing. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master's degree focused in Nursing Administration/Education from The University of Texas at Arlington.

Experience

JPMorgan Chase & Co. Corporate Health Nurse June 2019 - Present (1 year)

Memorial Hermann Health System Emergency Room Nurse July 2018 - Present (1 year 11 months) The Woodlands

HCA Gulf Coast Division 5 years 10 months Clinical Educator June 2017 - January 2018 (8 months) Conroe, Texas

Emergency Department

House Supervisor May 2015 - June 2017 (2 years 2 months) Conroe, Texas

House Supervisor

Registered Nurse

April 2012 - May 2015 (3 years 2 months)

Conroe, Texas

Emergency Department

Hennepin County Medical Center Registered Nurse

March 2011 - March 2012 (1 year 1 month)

Emergency Department

The University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston Assistant Nurse Manager

June 2006 - March 2011 (4 years 10 months)

Huntsville, Texas

Correctional Managed Care

Harris Health System Registered Nurse June 2001 - August 2006 (5 years 3 months) Houston, Texas

Ben Taub General Hospital ED

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington

Master's degree, Nursing Administration/Education · (2016 - 2018)

The University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston Bachelor's degree, Nursing Science · (1999 - 2001)

Sam Houston State University

Pre-Nursing Studies · (1996 - 1999)